Hello, I'm Abhinash, a CRP who takes
care of his clients. One of
my clients from those planets is
Raju. He's
an auto driver here in Raipur. Last month, when
he fell ill, he had to
stay in the hospital for five days for treatment. Due to this illness,
his earnings were stopped for five days. There was the
worry of the hospital and on top of that, there was the worry of
how he would manage his expenses after leaving the hospital. Then I reminded him
that he had
purchased ICICI Lombard Hotspot On Insurance from me.
He received a fixed amount from Notification Insurance for
five days. Just by submitting the
discharge certificate from the hospital and a simple
claim form, his claim was settled
and Rs. 2,500 for 15 days at the rate of ₹500 per day was credited to
his account
in 14 days. Not only this, he can get this for up
to 30 days of hospitalization in Bhopal.
Depending on the states, age and his choice, he had to pay approximately 262 rupees, in which
you can choose between
five days to
one day, approximately 500 rupees, depending on your heart's income and ability to pay.  You
can avail protection from Rs. 10,000 to Rs. 10,000.
For your information, keeping in mind the guidelines,
we have provided you some guidelines. You
can choose your policy from the following categories
and if you have to get hospitalized, you
can easily get treatment.
Therefore, I suggest that you advise all your
customers to take ICICI Lombard
insurance so that your
customers do
not have to worry about losing their income in case of hospitalization.
This insurance provides a fixed
amount per day which enriches their daily income
and provides them financial assistance.
For more information,
click on ICICI Lombard on the CSC portal today and
contact your relationship manager.
Now, this is the same thing, neither asafoetida nor alum is used, the
color remains bright. On my suggestion,
Raju bought ICICI Lombard General
Insurance and secured himself
and has left his customer Ajay insecure.